[Music]
Productivity increases when processes
are easy. So we improved usability in
the different areas within production
order handling. We added ability to
block output transactions. We add
attachments, edit in Excel,
uh and many more. Let's see them in the
demonstration. We begin with a planning
worksheet to create multiple production
orders and print reports for
them. Production orders can be bulk
moved between statuses. Select all and
use change
status. Most are converted. The rest
need analysis and action.
The production order includes a buffer
between the due date and end date based
on safety lead time in a manufacturing
setup or item card. Orders can be
rescheduled without changing the due
date. Moving the end date beyond the due
date will prompt a
confirmation. Remember to activate the
manual scheduling field on the
manufacturing setup page.
Attachments are now included in headers
and production order lines automatically
populated with information about items,
bills of material, and routing. The
business posting group code in the
production order can be defaulted to the
value defined in the default general
business posting group field on the
manufacturing setup
page. Availability information for
components is improved.
Select items can be used to add
additional
items. An overview of activities and
routings is enhanced. Routing link code
can also be updated within routings
affecting the start date for connected
components.
Consumption and output journals now
feature tracking and lines like the item
journal. The edit in Excel capability
can be utilized to populate item
tracking details.
Barcode labels can be printed for items
with tracking from both released and
finished production
orders. Thank you for watching. You can
find additional details about these
capabilities in the release note. Also
remember to watch other videos about
enhancements on manufacturing area. You
can find links in the description.